Guide to the David Plowden Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1948-2011; Series I; 189; 41.9 linear_feet
  - June 1999 Acquisition
    - Stephanie. Winnetka, Illinois (597-59), 1997 May (Box 131)
    - The Astoria Bridge, Columbia River. Astoria, Oregon to Point Ellice, Washington (GFB-68-2621), 1968 (Box 132)
    - Daniel Plowden. Stoneham, Massachusetts (697-312), 1997 June (Box 132)
    - Deborah Younce, "Little Deb". Acoaxet, Massachusetts (898-265), 1998 August (Box 132)
    - Gordon Younce. Winnetka, Illinois (US-990-41), 1990 September (Box 132)
    - Industrial Landscape Adjacent to Calumet River. South Chicago, Illinois (C-1082-130), 1982 October (Box 132)
    - Karen. Lakeview, New York (898-67), 1998 August (Box 132)
    - Karen. Winnetka, Illinois (US-PK-689-90), 1989 June (Box 132)
    - Karen, 609 Cherry Street. Winnetka, Illinois (US-PK 1089), 1989 October (Box 132)
    - Karen Plowden. Winnetka, Illinois (US-597-112), 1997 May (Box 132)
    - Mary Plowden (Mrs. Daniel). Stoneham, Massachusetts (697-10), 1997 June (Box 132)
    - Mother (Mary Butler Plowden). Evanston, Illinois (US-797-165), 1997 July (Box 132)
    - Nuclear Generating Plant. Braidwood, Illinois (C-1083-106), 1983 October (Box 132)
    - Philip. Winnetka, Illinois (US-PK-1089), 1989 October (Box 132)
    - Philip. Winnetka, Illinois (US-597-180), 1997 May (Box 132)
    - Sandra. Winnetka, Illinois (US-597-180), 1997 May (Box 132)
    - Benjamin Franklin Bridge, Delaware River. Between Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and Camden, New Jersey (1070-137), 1970 October (Box 133)
    - Bow Detail, Steamer J.M. Ford. Waukegan, Illinois (1085-214), 1985 October (Box 133)
    - Bronx Whitestone Bridge, East River. New York, New York (GFB-69-451), 1969 (Box 133)
    - The Carquinez Strait Bridge. Between Vallejo and Crockett, California (GFB-68-3088), 1968 (Box 133)
    - The Conde B. McCullough Memorial Bridge, Coos Bay. North Bend, Oregon (GFB-68-5788), 1968 (Box 133)
    - The Eugene A. Doran Memorial Bridge, San Mateo Creek. Two Miles West of San Mateo, California (972-533), 1972 September (Box 133)
    - Fred G. Redmon Memorial Bridge, Selah Creek. Yakima, Washington (972-303), 1972 September (Box 133)
    - Golden Gate Bridge. San Francisco, California (972-191), 1972 September (Box 133)
    - Golden Gate Bridge. San Francisco, California (972-326), 1972 September (Box 133)
    - Golden Gate Bridge, North Tower. San Francisco, California (972-665), 1972 September (Box 133)
    - Market Street Bridge, Susquehanna River. Harrisburg, Pennsylvania (GFB-469-29), 1969 April (Box 133)
    - Reading Company Railroad Bridge, Susquehanna River. Harrisburg, Pennsylvania (GFB-469-110), 1969 April (Box 133)
    - Richmond-San Rafael Bridge. San Pablo Bay, California (GFB-68-3081), 1968 (Box 133)
    - Second Canadian Pacific Railway Bridge (front), Canadian National Railway Bridge (back). Fraser River, Siska Creek, British Columbia, Canada (GFB-68-3262), 1968 (Box 133)
    - Weissport, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-225), 1963 October (Box 133)
    - Betty Sapir. New Hampshire (697-567), 1997 June (Box 134)
    - The Brooklyn Bridge, East River. New York, New York (173-137), 1973 January (Box 134)
    - The Clark Bridge, Mississippi River. Alton, Illinois (798-94), 1998 July (Box 134)
    - David McCullough. West Tisbury, Massachusetts (898-224), 1998 August (Box 134)
    - David Rathbun. Winnetka, Illinois (597-80), 1997 May (Box 134)
    - David Sapir. New Hampshire (697-658), 1997 June (Box 134)
    - Delaware and Hudson Railroad, Through Truss Bridge. West Pawlet, Vermont (V-663-170), 1963 June (Box 134)
    - Iron Truss (Pratt Truss), Cherry Valley Creek. Middlefield, New York (GFB-69-796), 1969 (Box 134)
    - Near Manteno, Will County, Illinois (698-9), 1998 June (Box 134)
    - Portal Detail, Iron Pratt Truss, Cherry Valley Creek. Middlefield, New York (GFB-69-678), 1969 (Box 134)
    - The Quincy Bridge, Mississippi River. Quincy, Illinois (798-107), 1998 July (Box 134)
    - The Schoharie Creek Aqueduct. Fort Hunter, New York (NYS-1067-5), 1967 October (Box 134)
    - Six Span Through Pennsylvania Truss Highway Bridge, Susquehanna River. Bloomsburg, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-214), 1963 October (Box 134)
    - St. Johnsbury and Lamoille County Railroad, Covered Railroad Bridge, Mississippi River (STJ-571-311), 1971 May (Box 134)
    - The Clark Bridge, Mississippi River. Alton, Illinois (798-25), 1998 July (Box 135)
    - The Clark Bridge, Mississippi River. Alton, Illinois (798-497), 1998 July (Box 135)
    - Elk Grove Village, Illinois (C-383-58), 1983 March (Box 135)
    - Elk Grove Village, Illinois (881-33), 1981 August (Box 135)
    - Exchange Street. Buffalo, New York (1085-2147), 1985 October (Box 135)
    - Former Great Western (Gulf, Mobile and Ohio RR) Bridge, Mississippi River. Between Louisiana and Missouri (798-350), 1998 July (Box 135)
    - Grain Elevator, Interior Detail. Dike, Iowa (1083-623), 1983 October (Box 135)
    - Jefferson Barracks Bridge, Mississippi River. I-255, South of Saint Louis, Missouri (798-265), 1998 July (Box 135)
    - MV Makim Gorky in Hudson River off New York City. New York, New York (JCM-952), 1975 (Box 135)
    - Oshkosh, Wisconsin (481-202), 1981 April (Box 135)
    - Plowed Wheat Field. Whitman County, Washington (972-641), 1972 September (Box 135)
    - Sandusky, Ohio (685-1219), 1985 June (Box 135)
    - Steamer J.B. Ford Unloading Cement. Waukegan, Illinois (1085-153), 1985 October (Box 135)
    - Tool Board, Steamer Keewatin. Port McNichol, Ontario, Canada (964-938), 1964 September (Box 135)
    - Ziggi's Tavern. Dubuque, Iowa (881-1213), 1981 August (Box 135)
    - Abandoned Textile Mill. Albion, Rhode Island (475-327), 1975 April (Box 136)
    - Barn and Corn Crib. Logan County, Illinois (373-21), 1973 March (Box 136)
    - Block Island, Rhode Island (BI-473-268), 1973 April (Box 136)
    - Buffalo, New York (1085-817), 1985 October (Box 136)
    - Calumet River. Chicago, Illinois (C-1082-437), 1982 October (Box 136)
    - Chicago, Illinois (881-1174), 1981 August (Box 136)
    - Elk Grove Village, Illinois (C-383-2), 1983 March (Box 136)
    - Fireman's Hall. Bessemer, Michigan (680-581), 1981 May (Box 136)
    - Industrial Park. Elk Grove Village, Illinois (C-383-102), 1983 March (Box 136)
    - The Mastadon Mill. Cohoes, New York (1076-62), 1976 October (Box 136)
    - Side of Barn. Sharpsburg, Maryland (1066-1255), 1966 October (Box 136)
    - Steamer J.B. Ford off Waukegan, Illinois (1085-64), 1985 October (Box 136)
    - Tank Farm. Near Dubuque, Iowa (881-901), 1981 August (Box 136)
    - Track Side Storage Building. Russell, Kansas (969-80), 1969 September (Box 136)
    - Tract House. Warrenville, Illinois (881-570), 1981 August (Box 136)
    - Abandoned Ore Carriers. Superior, Wisconsin (679-559), 1979 June (Box 137)
    - Abandoned Turbine, Mastadon Mill. Cohoes, New York (1076-122), 1976 October (Box 137)
    - Bridges, Narragansett Bay. Jameston, Rhode Island (798-640), 1998 July (Box 137)
    - Café Window. Lanark, Illinois (969-1250), 1969 September (Box 137)
    - Chicago, Illinois (1079-204), 1979 October (Box 137)
    - Counter Stern, Steamer Algosoo. Midland, Ontario, Canada (964-583), 1964 September (Box 137)
    - Doorway, Former New York Central Railroad. Newark, New York (WC-505), 1966 (Box 137)
    - Funnel Detail, Steamer J.B. Ford (1085-218), 1985 October (Box 137)
    - Schlitz Brewery Malt House. Milwaukee, Wisconsin (1085-87), 1985 October (Box 137)
    - Turbine, Mastadon Mill. Cohoes, New York (1076-77), 1976 October (Box 137)
    - Warehouse. Brooklyn, New York (173-15), 1973 January (Box 137)
  - July 2000 Acquisition
    Purchased from David Plowden on the Arthur Corbitt Hoskins Memorial Fund, 2000.
    - Abandoned Building, Butler Shipbuilders. Superior, Wisconsin (685-431), 1985 June (Box 138)
    - Abandoned Feed Mill. Pewamo, Michigan (899-327), 1999 August (Box 138)
    - Barn. Near Mount Pleasant, Michigan (975-1161), 1975 September (Box 138)
    - Cottonwood, South Dakota (GP-981), 1971 (Box 138)
    - Crane Boat SS William H. Donner. Milwaukee, Wisconsin (1085-113), 1985 October (Box 138)
    - Detail, Round Barn. South Hero, Vermont (275-105), 1975 February (Box 138)
    - Feed Mill and Store. Kent City, Michigan (1199-36), 1999 November (Box 138)
    - Gambral Roof Barn, Dairy Barn. Brookline, Windham County, Vermont (V-NH-865-135), 1965 August (Box 138)
    - Near Pisacho, Arizona (678-416), 1978 June (Box 138)
    - "Lippert" Building. Zeeland, Michigan (1199-122), 1999 November (Box 138)
    - Pekin, North Dakota (GP-1391), 1971 (Box 138)
    - Rear View of Moose Lodge. Lowell, Michigan (899-267), 1999 August (Box 138)
    - Round Barn. South Hero, Vermont (275-61), 1975 February (Box 138)
    - Side of Stone Barn. Chester County, Pennsylvania (475-486-A), 1975 April (Box 138)
    - SS Stravangerfjord, Norwegian American Line. New York, New York (NYH-863-99), 1963 August (Box 138)
    - Winn Shopping Center. Minneapolis, Michigan (899-135), 1999 August (Box 138)
    - Abandoned Farm (barn). Chester, Ottawa County, Michigan (1199-37), 1999 November (Box 139)
    - Abandoned Farmhouse. Near Piqua, Ohio (LFC-1855), 1964 (Box 139)
    - Abandoned Garage. Westmorland, Kansas (CP-1787), 1973 (Box 139)
    - Abandoned Grocery Store. Greenville, New Mexico (471-411), 1971 April (Box 139)
    - Abandoned Motel. Carbon County, Wyoming (874-1896), 1974 August (Box 139)
    - Barn Painting. La Grange, Indiana (975-1393), 1975 September (Box 139)
    - Barn with Tree. Olive, Ottawa County, Michigan (1199-105), 1999 November (Box 139)
    - Detail, Barn Door. Near Woorster, Ohio (CP-903), 1973 (Box 139)
    - Detail, Grain Elevator. Frederick, Oklahoma (GFB-68-2831), 1968 (Box 139)
    - Erosion. Grundy County, Iowa (583-104), 1983 May (Box 139)
    - Fence. Watrous, New Mexico (GFB-68-2944), 1968 (Box 139)
    - General Mills Elevator "A". Duluth, Minnesota (685-517 or 685-577), 1985 June (Box 139)
    - Mission De Abril. Watrous, New Mexico (GFB-68-2926), 1968 (Box 139)
    - Near Malta, Colorado (678-120), 1978 June (Box 139)
    - Near Montpelier, Ohio (971-88), 1971 September (Box 139)
    - Near Montpelier, Ohio (971-110), 1971 September (Box 139)
    - Plowed Wheat Fields. Whitman County, Wyoming (972-283), 1972 September (Box 139)
    - Storage Bins, General Mills Elevator "A". Duluth, Minnesota (685-1768), 1985 June (Box 139)
    - Abandoned Barn. Adams Township, Defiance County, Ohio (500-204), 2000 May (Box 140)
    - Abandoned Barn. Chester, Ottawa County, Michigan (1199-40), 1999 November (Box 140)
    - Abandoned Barn. Near Jamestown, Ottawa County, Michigan (1049-17), 1999 (Box 140)
    - Abandoned Barn with Windmill. Cotton County, Oklahoma (GFB-68-3907), 1968 (Box 140)
    - Abandoned Feed Mill by Delaware and Hudson Railroad Tracks. Unadilla, New York (699-577), 1999 June (Box 140)
    - Barn. Clare County, Michigan (975-945), 1975 September (Box 140)
    - Barn. Near Warren, Vermont (V-1065-162), 1965 October (Box 140)
    - Barn, Henry County Home. Near Napolean, Ohio (500-81), 2000 May (Box 140)
    - Detail, Abandoned Barn, Farm of Herman J. Leu. Near Tedrow, Fulton County, Ohio (500-399), 2000 May (Box 140)
    - Everett Peck's Barn. On United States Route 20, Northwest Township, Williams County, Ohio (500-586), 2000 May (Box 140)
    - Hayloft, Woodyvale Farm Barn, Richard Stevens Farm. Isabella County, Michigan (799-399), 1999 July (Box 140)
    - Oval Barn, Scott Manz, Owner. Forreston Township, Ogle County, Illinois (400-529), 2000 April (Box 140)
    - Post Office Block. New Hampshire (699-178), 1999 June (Box 140)
    - Stevens Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (799-475), 1999 July (Box 140)
    - Tuttle Block. Pittsfield, New Hampshire (699-449), 1999 June (Box 140)
    - ADM Mill. Buffalo, New York (899-597), 1999 August (Box 141)
    - Barn. Amble, Michigan (799-279), 1999 July (Box 141)
    - Barn. Clare County, Michigan (899-105), 1999 August (Box 141)
    - Barn Doors, Farm of Wm. Faber. Weidman, Michigan (899-24), 1999 August (Box 141)
    - Barn, Price Farm. New Hampshire (699-375), 1999 June (Box 141)
    - Barrie Barn. Bowne, Michigan (799-38), 1999 July (Box 141)
    - Bat Manor. Alton, New Hampshire (699-43), 1999 June (Box 141)
    - Building, Corner of Washington and Main Streets. Lowell, Michigan (799-198), 1999 July (Box 141)
    - Building, Corner of Washington and Main Streets. Lowell, Michigan (799-205), 1999 July (Box 141)
    - Doorway, Farmhouse. Beauty Hill Road, Town of Alton, New Hampshire (699-576), 1999 June (Box 141)
    - Ferguson Electric. Buffalo, New York (899-548), 1999 August (Box 141)
    - King Milling Company. Lowell, Michigan (799-258), 1999 July (Box 141)
    - Saint John, Michigan (899-219), 1999 August (Box 141)
    - Side of Bank. Pittsfield, New Hampshire (699-17), 1999 June (Box 141)
    - Universalist Church. South Strafford, Vermont (699-262), 1999 June (Box 141)
    - Bell Atlantic Company. Buffalo, New York (899-427), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Cemetery. East Palmyra, New York (WC-336), 1966 (Box 142)
    - Detail, Former Church. Alstead, New Hampshire (499-95), 1999 April (Box 142)
    - Farm. Jones County, Iowa (587-130), 1987 May (Box 142)
    - Former Church. Alstead, New Hampshire (499-120), 1999 April (Box 142)
    - Grain Elevator. Buffalo, New York (899-623), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Great Northern Elevator. Buffalo, New York (899-568), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Mural and Doorway, Side of Building. Corner of Kentucky and Republic Streets, Buffalo, New York (899-710), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Mural, Side of Building. Corner of Kentucky and Republic Streets, Buffalo, New York (899-735), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Mural, Side of Building. Corner of Kentucky and Republic Streets, Buffalo, New York (899-678), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Painted Lion on Side of Restaurant. On Delaware Avenue, Buffalo, New York (899-539), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Quincy, Illinois (798-40), 1998 July (Box 142)
    - Rear of Moose Lodge. Lowell, Michigan (899-310), 1999 August (Box 142)
    - Side of Former Jailhouse. Newfane, Vermont (499-55), 1999 April (Box 142)
    - Steven's Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (799-383), 1999 July (Box 142)
    - [Untitled]. Benwood, West Virginia (798-632), 1998 July (Box 143)
    - Abandoned Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (975-1499), 1975 September (Box 143)
    - Abandoned Ferry Boat, Brinkerhoff. Pawcatuck, Connecticut (CT-1263-11), 1963 (Box 143)
    - Block Island, Rhode Island (BI-473-249), 1973 April (Box 143)
    - Former Church, Union Hall. Newfane, Vermont (499-39), 1999 April (Box 143)
    - Former Town Hall. Charleston, New Hampshire (499-193), 1999 April (Box 143)
    - Power Shovel, Empire Mine. Palmer, Michigan (679-680), 1979 June (Box 143)
    - SS Flavenjerfjiord. New York (NYH-1163-102), 1963 November (Box 143)
    - Town House. Acworth, New Hampshire (499-161), 1999 April (Box 143)
    - "Uncle Sam". Muir, Michigan (889-346), 1989 August (Box 143)
    - Afterhouse and Funnel Detail, Steamer Crispin Oglebay. Fairport, Ohio (790-376), 1990 July (Box 144)
    - Bedroom Detail, Hotel Brooklyn. Brooklyn, Iowa (687-624), 1987 June (Box 144)
    - Canadian Pacific Railway, 4-6-2 Type Locomotive #2412, Last Day of Operation, The Glen Engine Terminal. Montreal, Quebec, Canada (CPR-360-2412), 1960 March (Box 144)
    - Detail, Crosshead, Canadian National Railway, Locomotive #6218. Montpelier Junction, Vermont (V-865-110), 1965 August (Box 144)
    - Former Jersey Central Railroad Depot. Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania (PA-1063-309), 1964 January (Box 144)
    - Former Tuttle Block. Pittsfield, New Hampshire (699-499), 1999 June (Box 144)
    - Funnel Detail, Steamer Henry Steinbrenner. Buffalo, New York (789-572), 1989 July (Box 144)
    - Grain Elevators Beside Northern Pacific Railway Tracks. Golden Valley, North Dakota (GP-253), 1971 (Box 144)
    - The Thomas Viaduct. Relay, Maryland (LFC-688), 1966 (Box 144)
    - Steamer, Kinsman Independent, Unloading Cement Clinker. Superior, Wisconsin (685-694), 1985 June (Box 144)
    - The Yaquina Bay Bridge. Newport, Oregon (GFB-68-5575), 1968 (Box 144)
  - July 2001 Acquisition
    Purchased from David Plowden on the Arthur Corbitt Hoskins Memorial Fund, 2001
    - Corner Detail, Ronald Groebner's Cow Barn. On County Road OK, Brodhead, Green County, Wisconsin (700-60), 2000 July (Box 145)
    - David Brown's Cow Barn. Jefferson Township, Green County, Wisconsin (300-635), 2000 March (Box 145)
    - David Brown's Cow Barn, Interior. Jefferson Township, Green County, Wisconsin (500-988), 2000 May (Box 145)
    - Detail, Dan Lincoln's Dairy Barn. Near Juda, Green County, Wisconsin (300-500), 2000 March (Box 145)
    - Detail, Stanchion, Unused Dairy Farm, Goodview Farm. Juda, Wisconsin (400-410), 2000 April (Box 145)
    - Farmland Looking West from County Highway X-47. One Mile North of Petersburg, Delaware County, Iowa (700-33), 2000 July (Box 145)
    - Interior Detail, David Brown's Barn. Jefferson Township, Green County, Wisconsin (300-599), 2000 March (Box 145)
    - Interior Detail, Gardner Family Cow Barn. Solon Mills, McHenry County, Illinois (900-314), 2000 September (Box 145)
    - Interior Detail, Gardner Family Farm, Cow Barn. Solon Mills, McHenry County, Illinois (900-12), 2000 September (Box 145)
    - Interior Detail, Windskell Home Farm. White Oak Springs Township, Lafayette County, Wisconsin (300-1104), 2000 March (Box 145)
    - Mills County. Near Hastings, Iowa (489-682), 1987 April (Box 145)
    - Near West Liberty. Cedar County, Iowa (487-749), 1987 April (Box 145)
    - Roof Detail, Round Barn Owned by Mrs. William Benson. On Route U.S. 20, West of Angola, Steuben County, Indiana (500-1446), 2000 May (Box 145)
    - Roof Detail, Round Barn Owned by Mrs. William Benson. On Route U.S. 20, West of Angola, Steuben County, Indiana (500-1470), 2000 May (Box 145)
    - Shovels, Duerst Barn. On Highway H, West of New Glarus, Green County, Wisconsin (300-68), 2000 March (Box 145)
    - Stanchions, Gardner Family Cow Barn. Solon Mills, McHenry County, Illinois (900-215), 2000 September (Box 145)
    - Stanchions, Ronald Groebner's Barn. Brodhead, Green County, Wisconsin (700-279), 2000 July (Box 145)
    - [Untitled]. Grundy County, Iowa (1083-1092), 1983 October (Box 146)
    - Barn Belonging to Herman Leu. On County Road H, Near Tedrow, Fulton County, Ohio (500-1082), 2000 May (Box 146)
    - Barn Interior, Hay Mow Showing Trusswork, "Gothic" Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (975-1039), 1975 September (Box 146)
    - Corn Crib Door, Genter Farm. German Township, Fulton County, Ohio (500-152), 2000 May (Box 146)
    - Detail Doors, Stone Barn, Henneberry Farm. On Cherry Road, Two Miles South of Oswego, Kendall County, Illinois (1000-239), 2000 October (Box 146)
    - Detail, Herman Leu's Barn. On County Road H, Near Tedrow, Fulton County, Ohio (500-853), 2000 May (Box 146)
    - Doughnut Barn, Detail of Interior (Doughnut). Baileyville, Ogle County, Illinois (400-269), 2000 April (Box 146)
    - Harold Knight's Barn. Strawberry Point, Clayton County, Iowa (700-44), 2000 July (Box 146)
    - Hay Mow, John Dieckhoff's Cow Barn. On Highway OK, Near Brodhead, Green County, Wisconsin (700-452), 2000 July (Box 146)
    - Interior Oval Barn. On Crane Grove Road, West of Baileyville, Forreston Township, Ogle County, Illinois (400-701), 2000 April (Box 146)
    - Milk House, Duerst Barn. On Highway H, West of New Glarus, Green County, Wisconsin (300-1104), 2000 March (Box 146)
    - Roof Detail, Prairie View Farm. Wolcottville, Noble County, Indiana (300-659), 2000 March (Box 146)
    - Threshing Bay Bank Barn on Farm Owned by Charles Lee Riddle and Son. Fulton County, Indiana (300-535), 2000 March (Box 146)
    - Window, Hexagon Barn. On Route U.S. 15, South of Bryan, Williams County, Ohio (500-120), 2000 May (Box 146)
    - Windskell Home Farm. White Oak Springs Township, Lafayette County, Wisconsin (300-688), 2000 March (Box 146)
    - Doorway Detail, Limestone Bank Barn. Three miles North of Plainfield, Will County, Illinois (1000-300), 2000 October (Box 147)
    - Doorway Detail, Limestone Bank Barn. Three Miles North of Plainfield, Will County, Illinois (1000-322), 2000 October (Box 147)
    - Gable End, Limestone Bank Barn. Three Miles North of Plainfield, Will County, Illinois (1000-262), 2000 October (Box 147)
    - Gable End, Limestone Bank Barn. Three Miles North of Plainfield, Will County, Illinois (1000-262), 2000 October (Box 147)
    - Limestone Bank Barn. Three Miles North of Plainfield, Will County, Illinois (1000-29), 2000 October (Box 147)
    - Limestone Bank Barn. Three Miles North of Plainfield, Will County, Illinois (1000-452), 2000 October (Box 147)
    - Barn Belonging to Tom and Verna Kintzle. On State Highway 38, Greeley, Delaware County, Iowa (700-200), 2000 July (Box 148)
    - Barn Owned by Roger Groves. On State Route 64, West of Polo, Buffalo Township, Ogle County, Illinois (400-473), 2000 April (Box 148)
    - Barnyard, Speich Brothers' Orford View Farm. Ofordville, Rock County, Wisonsin (300-181 or 300-187), 2000 March (Box 148)
    - Charles Riddle and Son's Farm. Richland Township,Fulton County, Indiana (300-167), 2000 March (Box 148)
    - Concrete Corn Crib. Naausay Township, Kendall County, Illinois (1000-554), 2000 October (Box 148)
    - Concrete Corn Crib. Naausay Township, Kendall County, Illinois (1000-529), 2000 October (Box 148)
    - Corn Crib and Barn on Farm Belonging to John Pihl. On Streight Road, Near Harvard, McHenry County, Illinois (800-54), 2000 August (Box 148)
    - Corn Crib, Cherry Farm. Oswego Township, Kendall County, Illinois (1000-101), 2000 October (Box 148)
    - Daniel Webber's Barn. Prairie Creek Township, Dubuque County, Iowa (700-552), 2000 July (Box 148)
    - "Doughnut" Barn Owned by James Karney. Baileyville, Ogle County, Illinois (400-75), 2000 April (Box 148)
    - John Coleman's Barn, Goodview Farm. Near Juda, Green County, Wisconsin (400-307), 2000 April (Box 148)
    - John Deickhoff's Barn. On Highway OK, Near Brodhead, Green County, Wisconsin (300-852), 2000 March (Box 148)
    - John Pihl's Barn. On Streight Road, Near Harvard, McHenry County, Illinois (800-124), 2000 August (Box 148)
    - Lester Scherbring's Barn. Near Earlville, Iowa (700-264), 2000 July (Box 148)
    - Perkins Farm. Town of Milford, Near Stroh, Lagrange County, Indiana (300-573), 2000 March (Box 148)
    - Richard Barber's Barn. Isabella County, Michigan (975-943), 1975 September (Box 148)
    - Silas Oval Barn. Leaf River, Ogle County, Illinois (400-587), 2000 April (Box 148)
    - The Gardner Farm, Cow Barn and Milk House. Solon Mills, McHenry County, Illinois (900-146), 2000 September (Box 148)
    - Abandoned Farm. Isabella County, Michigan (975-2212), 1975 September (Box 149)
    - Abandoned Farmstead. Hudsonville, Michigan (1099-84), 1999 October (Box 149)
    - Duerst Barn built 1883. On Highway H, West of New Glarus, Green County, Wisconsin (300-1144), 2000 March (Box 149)
    - Gerig Round Barn, built 1910 (abandoned). Henry Township, Fulton County, Indiana (300-216), 2000 March (Box 149)
    - Oval Barn Owned by Scott Manz. On Back Pocket Acres Crane Road, One Mile West of Baileyville, Forreston Township, Ogle County, Illinois (400-529), 2000 April (Box 149)
    - Radiator. Lake View, New York (1092-1076), 1992 October (Box 149)
    - Truelove/Norris Barn. Noble County, Albion, Indiana (300-534), 2000 March (Box 149)
    - Turkey Creek Barn (abandoned). Near Winona Lake, Kosciusko County, Indiana (300-244), 2000 March (Box 149)
    - Twin Barns Owned by Stephen Fry. On County Road W, Southwest of Archbold, Henry County, Ohio (500-1266), 2000 May (Box 149)